A Guide to the Robert and Wilva Breen Collection, 1933-1980
George Mason University Libraries
- The Robert Breen Collection
  - CORPORATE MEMBERSHIP: MEMBERSHIP PARTICIPATION., Folder 5 (Box Box 29)
  - ANTA - ORGANIZATION 1951., Folder 6 (Box Box 29)
  - ANTA - ORGANIZATION., Folder 7 (Box Box 29)
  - ANTA - ORGANIZATION., Folder 8 (Box Box 29)
  - ANTA: ORGANIZATIONAL CHART., Folder 9 (Box Box 29)
  - APPLICATIONS - STAFF., Folder 10 (Box Box 29)
  - CALENDAR 1951., Folder 11 (Box Box 29)
  - STAFF MEMOS., Folder 12 (Box Box 29)
  - STAFF WEEKLY WORK SHEETS., Folder 13 (Box Box 29)
  - BOB PORTERFIELD, 1944., Folder 1 (Box Box 30)
  - ENTERTAINMENT - DRAMA FORCES., Folder 2 (Box Box 30)
  - JOHN F. WHARTON., Folder 3 (Box Box 30)
  - BIBLIOGRAPHY - FILM, WITH NEWS PAPER CLIPPINGS 1942 - 45., Folder 4 (Box Box 30)
  - NATIONAL ARTS FOUNDATION PLAN., Folder 5 (Box Box 30)
  - THEATER FOUNDATION PLAN., Folder 6 (Box Box 30)
  - "EXPANSION OF THE THEATER HOW? (A PLAN FOR A PUBLIC THEATER FOUNDATION)., Folder 7 (Box Box 30)
  - CURRENT DIGEST OF BREEN - PORTERFIELD PLAN., Folder 8 (Box Box 30)
  - MARGARET DRAPER ( U.S. PUBLIC THEATER)., Folder 9 (Box Box 30)
  - ANTA - MULTIP - COP (ANTA FOUNDATION PLANS)., Folder 10 (Box Box 30)
  - PRESS (CORRESPONDENCE, JULY 1945 - DEC. 1945)., Folder 11 (Box Box 30)
  - PROGRESS REPORT 1945., Folder 12 (Box Box 30)
  - THEATER FOUNDATION FILE., Folder 13 (Box Box 30)
  - USP THEATER FOUNDATION PLAN OLD (REVISED MAY 31, 1945)., Folder 14 (Box Box 30)
  - US PUBLIC THEATER FOUNDATION PLAN OLD JULY 2, 1945., Folder 15 (Box Box 30)
  - ANTA - THEATER PLAN., Folder 16 (Box Box 30)
  - THEATER FOUNDATION PLAN., Folder 17 (Box Box 30)
  - AMERICAN NATIONAL THEATER FOUNDATION., Folder 18 (Box Box 30)
  - SUMMARY OF PROCEDURE TO PROVIDE NECESSARY FUNDS TO FORWARD ORG. PLAN., Folder 19 (Box Box 30)
  - BREEN: PORTERFIELD PLAN., Folder 1 (Box Box 31)
  - ANTA - FOUNDATION. PLAN (LETTERS; '45 - '46)., Folder 2 (Box Box 31)
  - THEATER FOUNDATION PLAN AND MISC., Folder 3 (Box Box 31)
  - THEATER FOUNDATION PLAN AND MEMORANDUM OF IMMEDIATE STEPS AND OBJ., Folder 4 (Box Box 31)
  - ANTA - THEATER PLAN (LETTERS; '45 - '46)., Folder 5 (Box Box 31)
  - THEATER UNION AND ORGANIZATIONS., Folder 6 (Box Box 31)
  - ANTA - FOUNDATION PLAN ('45 - '48)., Folder 7 (Box Box 31)
  - ANTA - FOUNDATION PLAN 1945 - 51., Folder 8 (Box Box 31)
  - DRAFTS ( FORM MATERIAL) 1946., Folder 9 (Box Box 31)
  - INTRA OFFICE MEMOS., Folder 10 (Box Box 31)
  - NEW YORK COMMITTEE FOR JUSTICE IN FREEPORT., Folder 11 (Box Box 31)
  - PUBLICITY., Folder 12 (Box Box 31)
  - "PLAN FOR UNEMPLOYMENT ACTORS"., Folder 13 (Box Box 31)
  - ANTA FOUNDATION PROPOSAL., Folder 14 (Box Box 31)
  - ANTA - FOUNDATION PLAN., Folder 15 (Box Box 31)
  - THE ANTA FOUNDATION JUNE 1948 - APRIL 1949., Folder 16 (Box Box 31)
  - JAVITS/FOUNDATION PLAN., Folder 17 (Box Box 31)
  - ANTA NATIONAL THEATER FOUNDATION, INTRODUCTION., Folder 18 (Box Box 31)
  - "A PLAN FOR A UNITED STATES PUBLIC THEATER FOUNDATION" BY BREEN'S PORTERFIELD., Folder 19 (Box Box 31)
  - BREEN. PORTERFIELD PLAN. DRAFTS., Folder 20 (Box Box 31)
  - THE ART COUNCIL BULLETIN., Folder 21 (Box Box 31)
  - ACADEMY PLANS., Folder 1 (Box Box 32)
  - "AUTHORS LEAGUE BULLETIN., Folder 2 (Box Box 32)
  - COPIES OF PREVIOUS PRESENTATIONS AND SUMMARIES., Folder 3 (Box Box 32)
  - THE GRADUATE ACADEMY PLAN., Folder 4 (Box Box 32)
  - STORY SNF PLAN OF ANTA 1946., Folder 5 (Box Box 32)
  - PROMOTION - SPEECHES., Folder 6 (Box Box 32)
  - ANTA PUBLICATIONS., Folder 7 (Box Box 32)
  - PHILOSOPHY, OBJ, SPONSORSHIP, FOUNDATION, ACTIVITIES OF ANTA., Folder 8 (Box Box 32)
  - BROCHURES., Folder 9 (Box Box 32)
  - THE NEW YORK TIMES - JULY 4, 1948 "INSIDE ANTA"., Folder 10 (Box Box 32)
  - "TWO MEMBERSHIP MEETINGS ON SEPT. 17TH IN EQUITY., Folder 11 (Box Box 32)
  - BY LAWS 1948 - 1951., Folder 1 (Box Box 33)
  - "ANTA IN ACTION" (BY G. FREEDLEY)., Folder 2 (Box Box 33)
  - THE AMERICAN NATIONAL THEATER - INTRODUCTION., Folder 3 (Box Box 33)
  - NEWS FROM HOME "ANTA THE FOUNDATION"., Folder 4 (Box Box 33)
  - ANTA (GENERAL NOTES) SEPT. 24, 1950., Folder 5 (Box Box 33)
  - ANTA CONTINUOUS DEPARTMENTAL WORK., Folder 6 (Box Box 33)
  - ANTA SERVICE TO THE THEATER "EVERYWHERE AND RECLAIMING THE AUDIENCES"., Folder 7 (Box Box 33)
  - ANTA - SUPPORT FOR ANTA IN ARTICLES, LETTERS, ETC., Folder 8 (Box Box 33)
  - REORGANIZATION LETTERS/PLANS., Folder 9 (Box Box 33)
  - WASHINGTON BOARD OF TRADE., Folder 10 (Box Box 33)
  - FINANCIAL DIFFICULTIES (ANTA) NEWSPAPER CLIPPING COPIES., Folder 11 (Box Box 33)
  - ANTA BY - LAWS., Folder 12 (Box Box 33)
  - CONSTITUTION OF THE ANTA., Folder 13 (Box Box 33)
  - ANTA FOUNDATION., Folder 14 (Box Box 33)
  - "WHAT IS ANTA" INTRODUCTION OF ANTA., Folder 15 (Box Box 33)
  - ANTA LISTING OF PROJECTS., Folder 16 (Box Box 33)
  - PLAN OF WORK FOR 2 YEAR COURSE IN ANTA., Folder 17 (Box Box 33)
  - US CONGRESS CHARTER - CREATING THE ANTA., Folder 1 (Box Box 34)
  - CHARTER GRANTED BY US CONGRESS CREATING: ANTA., Folder 2 (Box Box 34)
  - ANTA 1935 - 1949., Folder 3 (Box Box 34)
  - SENATE BILL 2642 AS PASSED BY THE CONGRESS OF THE UNITED STATES, JULY 5, 1935., Folder 4 (Box Box 34)
  - U.S. CONGRESS., Folder 5 (Box Box 34)
  - ANTA - FOUNDATION - WASHINGTON CORRESPONDENCE RE: CONG. SUPPORT FOR PLAN., Folder 6 (Box Box 34)
  - CONGRESSIONAL RECORD 1945., Folder 7 (Box Box 34)
  - HEARING BEFORE A SUBCOMMITTEE ON EDUCATION AND LABOR., Folder 8 (Box Box 34)
  - ANTA - WASH. D.C. - CONGRESSIONAL LISTS ('45 - '46)., Folder 9 (Box Box 34)
  - U.S. CONGRESSMEN., Folder 10 (Box Box 34)
  - CONGRESSIONAL RECORD 1948., Folder 11 (Box Box 34)
  - U.S. CONGRESS., Folder 12 (Box Box 33)
  - IVES SENATE JOINT RESOLUTION., Folder 13 (Box Box 34)
  - JAVITS BILL 1949., Folder 1 (Box Box 35)
  - JAVITS / BILL: NATURAL THEATER, OPERA, BULLET., Folder 2 (Box Box 35)
  - JAVITS GENERAL FILE., Folder 3 (Box Box 35)
  - JAVITS BILL - PUBLICITY., Folder 4 (Box Box 35)
  - 3 ANTA NEWSLETTERS; CONG. RECORD., Folder 5 (Box Box 35)
  - SENATORS AND CONGRESS EXTRA COPIES., Folder 1 (Box Box 36)
  - SENATORS AND CONGRESSMEN - GENERAL., Folder 2 (Box Box 36)
  - SENATORS AND CONGRESS FILM CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 3 (Box Box 36)
  - SENATORS AND CONGRESS FILM CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 4 (Box Box 36)
  - PRESENTATION., Folder 5 (Box Box 36)
  - JAVITS BILL CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 6 (Box Box 36)
  - JAVITS BILL PHOTO COPIES., Folder 7 (Box Box 36)
  - DRAFT COPY OF JAVITS BILL., Folder 8 (Box Box 36)
  - ANTA MISC., Folder 9 (Box Box 36)
  - JAVITS., Folder 10 (Box Box 36)
  - NATIONAL THEATER (JAVITS BILL)., Folder 11 (Box Box 36)
  - CORRESPONDENT CITIZEN'S COMMITTEE OF THE ARTS, SCIENCES AND PROFESSIONS., Folder 12 (Box Box 36)
  - A PLAN TO ESTABLISH THE AMERICAN THEATER ABD ACADEMY 1951., Folder 1 (Box Box 37)
  - TH BARTER THEATER, CERTIFICATE OF INCORPORATION., Folder 2 (Box Box 37)
  - BARTER THEATER., Folder 3 (Box Box 37)
  - BARTER - THEATER REPORT AND MISC. CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 4 (Box Box 37)
  - BARTER - STATEMENT., Folder 5 (Box Box 37)
  - REGISTRY - TALENT ' 48., Folder 6 (Box Box 37)
  - ACADEMY - INFO., Folder 7 (Box Box 37)
  - ACADEMY - TEACHER'S APPL., Folder 8 (Box Box 37)
  - ANTA - READINGS FOR AUDITIONS., Folder 9 (Box Box 37)
  - CHILD THEATER., Folder 10 (Box Box 37)
  - WOODROW WILSON FILM NOTES / PRIOR TO SCRIPT / 1941., Folder 1 (Box Box 38)
  - EXPER. THEATER BACKGROUND., Folder 2 (Box Box 38)
  - EDPER. THEATER BACKGROUND., Folder 3 (Box Box 38)
  - EXPER. THEATER BOARD., Folder 4 (Box Box 38)
  - EXPER. THEATER EQUIPMENT., Folder 5 (Box Box 38)
  - EXPER. THEATER., Folder 6 (Box Box 38)
  - EXPER. THEATER ACTORS SURVEY., Folder 7 (Box Box 38)
  - EXPER. THEATER., Folder 8 (Box Box 38)
  - EXPER. THEATER GENERAL., Folder 9 (Box Box 38)
  - EXPER. THEATER MAILING PIECES., Folder 10 (Box Box 38)
  - MAP - PLAYBILLS PLUS "SKIPPER NEXT TO GOD" PLUS THEATER QUESTIONNAIRE., Folder 11 (Box Box 38)
  - LETTER FROM R. BREEN TO BELIEVING RE: EXP. THEATER APR. 18, 1948., Folder 12 (Box Box 38)
  - BALLET BALLEDS 1947 - 1948 (EXPERIMENTAL THEATER)., Folder 1 (Box Box 39)
  - BALLET BALLEDS 1947 - 1948 (EXPERIMENTAL THEATER)., Folder 2 (Box Box 39)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER., Folder 3 (Box Box 39)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER., Folder 4 (Box Box 39)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER AUDIENCE RESEARCH 1947 - 1948.., Folder 5 (Box Box 39)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER AUDIENCE RESEARCH 1947 - 1948., Folder 6 (Box Box 39)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER AUDIENCE RESEARCH 1947 - 1948., Folder 7 (Box Box 39)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER., Folder 8 (Box Box 39)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER FINANCE BUDGET STATEMENT., Folder 9 (Box Box 39)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER MAILING PIECES., Folder 10 (Box Box 39)
  - E.T. SURVEY - LISTS - ACTORS AND PLAYS., Folder 11 (Box Box 39)
  - EXPER. THEATER INVITATIONAL SERIES., Folder 1 (Box Box 40)
  - BILL BUTLER - FILING SUBJECT CATEGORIES SUBJECT FILING., Folder 2 (Box Box 40)
  - EXPER. THEATER (DAILY)., Folder 3 (Box Box 40)
  - EXPER. THEATER MARTHA GRAHAM PERFS., Folder 4 (Box Box 40)
  - ANTA 1948 EXPER. THEATER MARTHA GRAHAM PERFS., Folder 5 (Box Box 40)
  - EXPER. THEATER., Folder 6 (Box Box 40)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER BUDGET FINANCE STATEMENTS., Folder 7 (Box Box 40)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER PRODUCTION CONTRACT AND ACTOR CONTRACT., Folder 8 (Box Box 40)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER PRODUCTION CONTRACTS AND ACTOR CONTRACT (PRESERVATION COPY)., Folder 9 (Box Box 40)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER AND ASSEM..., Folder 10 (Box Box 40)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER SUBSCRIPTION MEMOS., Folder 11 (Box Box 40)
  - FAMILY PORTRAIT., Folder 12 (Box Box 40)
  - HIPPODROME THEATER., Folder 1 (Box Box 41)
  - HIPPODROME / SITE / THEATER CENTRE - THEATER CITY., Folder 2 (Box Box 41)
  - HUDSON THEATER., Folder 3 (Box Box 41)
  - ANTA MISC. ( A EXPERT FROM SEASON IN AND SEASON OUT)., Folder 4 (Box Box 41)
  - ANTA ALBUM 1950 - XEROX COPIES., Folder 6 (Box Box 41)
  - ANTA - ALBUM MAY, 1951., Folder 7 (Box Box 41)
  - DECCA RECORD ALBUM - REPORT., Folder 8 (Box Box 41)
  - WALD - KRASNA "ANTA ALBUM" / CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 9 (Box Box 41)
  - FILMS: WALD - KRASNA "ANTA ALBUM" CLIPPINGS., Folder 10 (Box Box 41)
  - HIGOG - TOURS 1949., Folder 1 (Box Box 42)
  - HICOG - TOURS 1950., Folder 2 (Box Box 42)
  - ANDERSON JUDITH., Folder 3 (Box Box 42)
  - BERLIN FESTIVAL CORRESPONDENCE AND REPORT., Folder 4 (Box Box 42)
  - HICOG - BERLIN FESTIVAL., Folder 5 (Box Box 42)
  - HICOG - BERLIN FESTIVAL., Folder 6 (Box Box 42)
  - CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 1 (Box Box 43)
  - CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 2 (Box Box 43)
  - ANTA - L. JOUVET., Folder 3 (Box Box 43)
  - ANTA AND JOUVET COM. LIASON'S., Folder 4 (Box Box 43)
  - CORRESPONDENCE FROM CHERYL CRAWFORS PLUS ROBERT BREEN., Folder 5 (Box Box 43)
  - CORRESPONDENCE CHERY CRAWFORD PLUS ROBERT BREEN., Folder 6 (Box Box 43)
  - CORRESPONDENCE FROM ELIE EDSON., Folder 7 (Box Box 43)
  - CORRESPONDENCE FROM WILVA PLUS ROBERT BREEN., Folder 1 (Box Box 44)
  - CORRESPONDENCE FROM WILVA PLUS ROBERT BREEN., Folder 2 (Box Box 44)
  - L. JAUVAT BACKGROUND., Folder 3 (Box Box 44)
  - L. JAUVAT BACKGROUND., Folder 4 (Box Box 44)
  - LOUIS JOVUET INFOMATION IN FRENCH PLUS TRANSLATION., Folder 5 (Box Box 44)
  - LOUIS JOVUET INFORMATION IN FRENCH PLUS TRANSLATION., Folder 6 (Box Box 44)
  - LOVIS JAUVET "THE SCHOOL FOR WIVES" FLIERS PLUS CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 1 (Box Box 45)
  - MISC. 2 JAUVET., Folder 2 (Box Box 45)
  - ANTA PRESS RELEASES., Folder 3 (Box Box 45)
  - PUBLIC PAPERS ABOUT "THE SCHOOL FOR WIVES" AND JAUVET., Folder 4 (Box Box 45)
  - JAUVET GRANT SERVICE., Folder 5 (Box Box 45)
  - "MARY ROSE"., Folder 1 (Box Box 46)
  - "MARY ROSE"., Folder 2 (Box Box 46)
  - LIFE ARTICLE "BALLET BALLADS"., Folder 3 (Box Box 46)
  - BALLET THEATER, COVENT GARDEN CONTRACT., Folder 4 (Box Box 46)
  - BALLET THEATER / 1950 / EUROPEAN TOUR., Folder 5 (Box Box 46)
  - BALLET THEATER / 1950 / EUROPEAN TOUR., Folder 6 (Box Box 46)
  - BALLET THEATER TOUR: EUROPE, BELGIUM, HOLLAND, SCANDINAVIA., Folder 7 (Box Box 46)
  - (AMERICAN NATIONAL) BALLET THEATER EUROPEAN TOUR 1950 CONSULAR REPORTS AUG 7 TO DEC 10, 1950., Folder 8 (Box Box 46)
  - BALLET THEATER TOUR - EUROPE, ENGLAND - SCOTLAND., Folder 9 (Box Box 46)
  - BALLET THEATER TOUR - FRANCE., Folder 10 (Box Box 46)
  - BALLET THEATER TOUR - 1950 - GERMANY., Folder 11 (Box Box 46)
  - BALLET THEATER TOUR - ITALY, EGYPT., Folder 1 (Box Box 47)
  - BALLET THEATER - MEMOS, GENERAL., Folder 2 (Box Box 47)
  - BALLET THEATER / TRANSPORTATION JULY 1950., Folder 3 (Box Box 47)
  - BALLET 1950 THEATER / U.S. TOUR., Folder 4 (Box Box 47)
  - BALLET THEATER TOUR (ENVELOPE W/ LETTERS)., Folder 5 (Box Box 47)
  - (NATL) BALLET TOUR - MISC. MATERIAL., Folder 6 (Box Box 47)
  - DAVIS, BLEVINS., Folder 7 (Box Box 47)
  - DAVIS, BELVINS. (ANTA - BALLET)., Folder 8 (Box Box 47)
  - DAVIS, BLEVINS MEMOSTO TRUMAN., Folder 9 (Box Box 47)
  - PLAY BILLS., Folder 10 (Box Box 47)
  - FINA INFO (MISC.) RE. 1950 PLAY SERIES., Folder 11 (Box Box 47)
  - PROGRAM BOOK., Folder 12 (Box Box 47)
  - TO NEEL PLAN STADS SCHOUWBURG THEATER, AMSTERDAM ETC., Folder 13 (Box Box 47)
  - MISC. ITEMS, INCL. CONTRACT FOR GUEST PRODUCERS., Folder 14 (Box Box 47)
  - BALLET THEATER SOUTH AMERICAN TOUR 1951., Folder 15 (Box Box 47)
  - (MISC) FINANCIAL INFO. RE 1950 - 51. PLAY SERIES., Folder 16 (Box Box 47)
  - FIN. SUMMARY AND CORRESPOND BETWEEN BREEN / R. STEVENS., Folder 17 (Box Box 47)
  - BALLET THEATER CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 18 (Box Box 47)
  - SCRIPTS INFORMATION ON SCRIPTS IRVING PLACE 1938, 40., Folder 1 (Box Box 48)
  - TOURS - ALUGHTON., Folder 2 (Box Box 48)
  - TOURS - ALUGHTON., Folder 3 (Box Box 48)
  - LAUGHTON - TOUR - GALILEO., Folder 4 (Box Box 48)
  - ANTA: MOMOS; MISC. LETTERS AND PLAYHOUSE., Folder 5 (Box Box 48)
  - CRITICS - DRAMA EDITORS., Folder 6 (Box Box 48)
  - PLAY SERIES / HOUSE OPERATION., Folder 7 (Box Box 48)
  - PLAY SERIES AND PLAYHOUSE OPERATION, Folder 8 (Box Box 48)
  - PLAYHOUSE SERIES MAILING LISTS., Folder 9 (Box Box 48)
  - PLAY SERIES - PUBLICITY 1950., Folder 10 (Box Box 48)
  - PLAYHOUSE SERIES: PRESENTATION., Folder 11 (Box Box 48)
  - PLAYHOUSE SERIES SUBSCRIPTION REPORTS., Folder 12 (Box Box 48)
  - PLAYHOUSE SERIES SUBSCRIPTION MAILING SELLING LISTS., Folder 13 (Box Box 48)
  - PRODUCTION CONTACT - JEFFERS - TOWER, Folder 14 (Box Box 48)
  - REVIEWS - "TOWER BEYOND TRAGEDY" NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS., Folder 15 (Box Box 48)
  - SUBSCRIPTION MEMBERSHIP DIRECT CONTACT CAMPAIGN., Folder 16 (Box Box 48)
  - PERFORMANCE SCHEDULE 1950 - 1951., Folder 17 (Box Box 48)
  - PLAYHOUSE SERIES MEMO CAMP. PLAY BILLS, STATEMENTS, PLAY SERIES ETC., Folder 18 (Box Box 48)
  - PLAYHOUSE - COSTS - SCALING - INCOME., Folder 19 (Box Box 48)
  - ANTA - PLAY SERIES., Folder 20 (Box Box 48)
  - ANTA - PLAY SERIES., Folder 21 (Box Box 48)
  - ANTA PLAY SERIES / APS / TAXES: INTERNAL REVENUE DEPT. / (TAX)., Folder 1 (Box Box 49)
  - ANTA PLAY SERIES 1950 - 1951., Folder 2 (Box Box 49)
  - ANTA - PLAY SERIES MEMBERSHIP. FINANCIAL, STATEMENTS ECT., Folder 3 (Box Box 49)
  - ANTA - PLAY SERIES 1950 - 51., Folder 4 (Box Box 49)
  - ANTA - PLAY SERIES 1950 - 1951 "THE TOWER BEYOND TRAGEDY"., Folder 5 (Box Box 49)
  - (ANTA) "TWENTIETH CENTURY" - GALLEY PROOFS., Folder 6 (Box Box 49)
  - ANTA - PLAY SERIES 1950 - 1951 "TOWER BEYOND TRAGEDY", Folder 7 (Box Box 49)
  - FIRST ANTA PLAY SERIES 1950 - 1951., Folder 8 (Box Box 49)
  - ANTA - PLAY SERIES 1950 - 1951 SUBSCRIPTION MEMO., Folder 9 (Box Box 49)
  - ANTA - 'SHOWTIME' TV SERIES., Folder 10 (Box Box 49)
  - ANTA - 'SHOWTIME' TV SERIES., Folder 11 (Box Box 49)
  - PLAYS GENERAL 1950 - 52., Folder 12 (Box Box 49)
  - APS - NOTES ON: ANTA PLAY SERIES - ROBERT BREEN., Folder 13 (Box Box 49)
  - PLAY SERIES - PUBLIC RELATIONS., Folder 14 (Box Box 49)
  - PLAY SERIES - REPORTS., Folder 15 (Box Box 49)
  - PLAY SERIES., Folder 16 (Box Box 49)
  - PLAY SERIES., Folder 1 (Box Box 50)
  - FINANCIAL STATEMENTS - SALARY LIST ETC., Folder 2 (Box Box 50)
  - ANAT - PLAY SERIES., Folder 3 (Box Box 50)
  - ANTA - PLAY SERIES., Folder 4 (Box Box 50)
  - (ANTA) PLAY SERIES 1951., Folder 5 (Box Box 50)
  - (ANTA) - PLAY SERIES - STATEMENTS., Folder 6 (Box Box 50)
  - REPORTS ON PLAYS., Folder 7 (Box Box 50)
  - ANTA MISC., Folder 8 (Box Box 50)
  - ANTA PLAY SERIES 1952., Folder 9 (Box Box 50)
  - TAX EXEMPTION LETTER FROM THE DEPUTY COMMISSIONER OF INTERNAL REVENUE., Folder 1 (Box Box 51)
  - PLAY SERIES., Folder 2 (Box Box 51)
  - SURVEY RPT. ON THEATERS BY BERNAYS., Folder 3 (Box Box 51)
  - ANTA HAND WRITTEN NOTES - PLAYHOUSE AND PLAY SERIES., Folder 4 (Box Box 51)
  - ANTA - NOTES TO MEMBERSHIP., Folder 5 (Box Box 51)
  - ANTA - "PEER GYNT"., Folder 6 (Box Box 51)
  - ANTA PLAYHOUSE ANTA PLAY SERIES 1950 - 1951., Folder 7 (Box Box 51)
  - ANTA - PLAY SERIES (FN. RECORD; '50 - '51)., Folder 8 (Box Box 51)
  - ANTA - PLAY SERIES ("SCOREBOARD"; '50 - '51)., Folder 9 (Box Box 51)
  - TAX ON PLAY SERIES MEMBERSHIP., Folder 10 (Box Box 51)
  - TOWER BEYOND TRAGEDY., Folder 11 (Box Box 51)
  - ODETS / NIGHT MUSIC REVIEWS., Folder 12 (Box Box 51)
  - ANTA - PEER GYNT., Folder 13 (Box Box 51)
  - ANTA PLAY SERIES BRIEF APR. 9, 1951., Folder 14 (Box Box 51)
  - PLAY SERIES BULLETIN. FLYER FOR " GETTING MARRIED"., Folder 15 (Box Box 51)
  - ANTA TO: NY PRODUCERS AND FROM: ANTA PLAY SERIES COMMITTEE., Folder 16 (Box Box 51)
  - PLAY FOR JUDITH ANDERSON., Folder 17 (Box Box 51)
  - ANTA - "ADAM'S APPLE" SCRIPT., Folder 1 (Box Box 52)
  - THE ASSASSINS SCREEN PLAY NICK PROFERES., Folder 2 (Box Box 52)
  - THE BACHELOR QUEEN - LAWTON CAMPBELL., Folder 3 (Box Box 52)
  - BEGGARS HOLIDAY., Folder 4 (Box Box 52)
  - REVIEWS OF BEGGAR'S HOLIDAY., Folder 5 (Box Box 52)
  - READINGS FROM THE BOOK OF TRANS ERNEST DICK., Folder 6 (Box Box 52)
  - THE BROTHERS PANDAUAS., Folder 7 (Box Box 52)
  - BUTTON BUTTON., Folder 8 (Box Box 52)
  - CARMEN JONES - SCREENPLAY HARRY KLEMER., Folder 1 (Box Box 53)
  - CLERAMBARD - MARCEL AYME., Folder 2 (Box Box 53)
  - COURT J.M. GUNN., Folder 3 (Box Box 53)
  - COURT OR AMICUS CURIAC JAMES MASSON GUNN., Folder 4 (Box Box 53)
  - "CYPRIAN'S PRAYER" EDMUND WILSON., Folder 5 (Box Box 53)
  - DARK OF THE MOON. H. RISCHARDSON., Folder 6 (Box Box 53)
  - DEAR INTERNAL REVENUE SERVICE J.M. GUNN., Folder 7 (Box Box 53)
  - THE DEATH OF DON JUAN., Folder 8 (Box Box 53)
  - THE DEUCE., Folder 9 (Box Box 53)
  - DIGGIN THE BIG TIME. A ONE QACT OPERA., Folder 10 (Box Box 53)
  - A DREAM PALY AUGUST STRING BERG., Folder 11 (Box Box 53)
  - ELIJAH: THE SNOWBOUND HORSE REBECCA TURNER., Folder 1 (Box Box 54)
  - THE ENEMY ERNEST PICK., Folder 2 (Box Box 54)
  - "GET AWAY OLD MAN", Folder 3 (Box Box 54)
  - "GOD'S LITTLE ACRE" SCREENPLAY PHILIP YORDAN., Folder 4 (Box Box 54)
  - THE GREAT WORLD THEATER HUGO VAN HOFMANNSTHAL., Folder 5 (Box Box 54)
  - A GREAT ONE FOR FLOWERS., Folder 6 (Box Box 54)
  - HALF - WAY HONEYMOON - SIDNEY HARMON., Folder 7 (Box Box 54)
  - HEADLINES FROM HEAVEN - LAWTON CAMPBELL., Folder 8 (Box Box 54)
  - "HEADLINES FROM HEAVEN" - LAWTON CAMPBELL., Folder 9 (Box Box 54)
  - HEDDA GABLER., Folder 10 (Box Box 54)
  - THE VINEYARD AND THE PEEPERS OF THE WALLS - CHARLES FRINK., Folder 11 (Box Box 54)
  - THE HOUSE THAT SACK BUILT., Folder 12 (Box Box 54)
  - HUON OF BORDEAUY., Folder 13 (Box Box 54)
  - IBSENS PEER GYNT., Folder 1 (Box Box 55)
  - IBSEN'S PEER GYNT BY PAUL GREEN., Folder 2 (Box Box 55)
  - "IMPACT" DAUG HUDELSON., Folder 3 (Box Box 55)
  - "IN THE SUMMER HOUSE" JANE BAULES., Folder 4 (Box Box 55)
  - THE INDIAN CAPTURE., Folder 5 (Box Box 55)
  - INQUIRE WITHIN ('THESE DEAR RUINS") PETER FARRAS AND DIANE LAMBERT., Folder 6 (Box Box 55)
  - THE IRON CORONET - ALEVINE AND TOBY PERKINS, Folder 7 (Box Box 55)
  - "ISLAND FESTIVAL" (TENTATIVE TITLE), Folder 8 (Box Box 55)
  - JOHNNY APPLESEED - CHARLES FRINK., Folder 9 (Box Box 5)
  - A JOURNEY FROM THE RIVER, Folder 10 (Box Box 55)
  - JUDAS MARCEL PAGNAL., Folder 11 (Box Box 66)
  - MAN INTO ASHES ARTHUR WILMURT., Folder 1 (Box Box 57)
  - MARRY ROSE, Folder 2 (Box Box 57)
  - MORE THEN A NATION - ALICE CHILDRESS., Folder 3 (Box Box 57)
  - Mr. PICKWICK STANLEY GANG., Folder 4 (Box Box 57)
  - MUD RIVER ODYSSEY - MANUEL ESSMA., Folder 5 (Box Box 57)
  - MY AUNT THE OLD MAID - JAN PLUS LUIS QUINTAMILLA., Folder 6 (Box Box 57)
  - MY GOD! MY GOD IS DEAD., Folder 7 (Box Box 57)
  - MY PRINCE! MY RING, Folder 8 (Box Box 57)
  - THE NEW EMOTION - TOM DONNELY., Folder 1 (Box Box 58)
  - A NIGHT AT MADAM TUSSAUA'S - A PLAY., Folder 2 (Box Box 58)
  - THE NIGHT THAT MURIEL HIT 3RD STREET EDWARD USHER., Folder 3 (Box Box 58)
  - THE 19th WHOLE OF EUROPE., Folder 4 (Box Box 58)
  - THE OLD BYSTANDER - HARRY GRANICK., Folder 5 (Box Box 58)
  - THE ORBIS FAMILY BY CAROLINE SLADE ABD HARTENSE ALDEN., Folder 6 (Box Box 58)
  - OUR OWN FAMILY TREE A HARLEM SAGA BY ADA SANDERS., Folder 7 (Box Box 58)
  - PADRIAE AND THE HERO LOAMI RANDALL., Folder 8 (Box Box 58)
  - THE PATRIOTS OF NANTUCKET BY OSCAR MANDEL., Folder 9 (Box Box 58)
  - PELICAN BY DAVID SHUMAKER., Folder 10 (Box Box 58)
  - PHIPPS BY P.G. WODEHOUSE., Folder 11 (Box Box 58)
  - THE PLAYS THE THING., Folder 12 (Box Box 58)
  - RIGH - O - WAY A. WEBER., Folder 1 (Box Box 59)
  - SALOME- RICHARD STRAUSS., Folder 2 (Box Box 59)
  - THE SESSIONS OF CONRAD MARLAM., Folder 3 (Box Box 59)
  - SET FOR LIFE HAWARD RICHARDSON PLUS FRANCES GOFORTH., Folder 4 (Box Box 59)
  - THE SHADOW BOWSERS., Folder 5 (Box Box 59)
  - SHAUT UP A MORNING. A LEGEND OF JOHN HENRY., Folder 6 (Box Box 59)
  - SIGNS OF LIFE JAMES AUKER., Folder 7 (Box Box 59)
  - SIGNS OF WINTER ETTARE RELLA., Folder 8 (Box Box 59)
  - SOME THING WILD IN THE CITY., Folder 9 (Box Box 59)
  - SANATA FOR SMALL ORCHESTRA JM GUNN., Folder 1 (Box Box 60)
  - THE STEEPLE., Folder 2 (Box Box 60)
  - THE SUNDAYS OF SATIN LEGS SMITH BY WARREN COLEMAN., Folder 3 (Box Box 60)
  - TA, Mrs. JONES, WELL SEND YOU A CARD FROM THE FALLS ERNEST PICK., Folder 4 (Box Box 60)
  - THE TAILOR SUIT PETER FARRAU., Folder 5 (Box Box 60)
  - TAIL WAGS DAWG., Folder 6 (Box Box 60)
  - TAIL WAGS DOG BY KATHARINE CLUGSTON., Folder 7 (Box Box 60)
  - A TANGLEWOOD LOVE STORY BY JAMES AGEE AND HOWARD TAUBMAN., Folder 8 (Box Box 60)
  - A TANGLEWOOD LOVE STORY JAMES AGEE AND HOWARD TAWBMAN., Folder 9 (Box Box 60)
  - TANGLEWOOD - NOTES BY BREEN., Folder 1 (Box Box 61)
  - TEN GIRLS AGO - FARRAW PLUS DIANE LAMPERT., Folder 2 (Box Box 61)
  - THREE QUEENS MONTGOMERY HARE., Folder 3 (Box Box 61)
  - TOUCH STONE HALEN FRAENKEL., Folder 4 (Box Box 61)
  - THE TOWER BEYOND TRAGEDY., Folder 5 (Box Box 61)
  - TRIPLEK RONALD GROSS., Folder 6 (Box Box 61)
  - TRISKELION J M GUNN., Folder 7 (Box Box 61)
  - TWENTY THIRD AND OBLIVION., Folder 8 (Box Box 61)
  - VOLTE - FACE WILLIAM R. GREBE., Folder 1 (Box Box 62)
  - THE WANHOPE BUILDING., Folder 2 (Box Box 62)
  - THE WANHOPE BUILDING - JOHN FINCH., Folder 3 (Box Box 62)
  - THE WAR WILL NOT TAKE PLACE., Folder 4 (Box Box 62)
  - WILLY., Folder 4 (Box Box 62)
  - THE WELLS OF HARROW., Folder 5 (Box Box 62)
  - "WHAT A DAY FOR A MIRACLE"., Folder 6 (Box Box 62)
  - "ZERO" FRED STEWART., Folder 7 (Box Box 62)
  - OUTLINE FOR A ZERO., Folder 8 (Box Box 62)
  - ZULEIKA., Folder 9 (Box Box 62)
  - DARK TOWER REVIEWS., Folder 1 (Box Box 63)
  - 2Oth CENTURY REVIEWS (NY TIMES, CAMPUS AND HARALD) TRIB, Folder 2 (Box Box 63)
  - NIGHT MUSIC REVIEWS., Folder 3 (Box Box 63)
  - PEER GYNT REVIEWS., Folder 4 (Box Box 63)
  - MISC. PLAY SERIES., Folder 5 (Box Box 63)
  - ACCOUNT STATEMENTS PLAY SERIES AND OTHER - 1951., Folder 6 (Box Box 63)
  - ANTA - REGIONAL 1938 - 43., Folder 1 (Box Box 64)
  - REGION INFO 1951., Folder 2 (Box Box 64)
  - ANAT - VETERAN'S THEATER - US0 NEWS CLIPPINGS., Folder 3 (Box Box 64)
  - ANTA PROJECTS 1946., Folder 4 (Box Box 64)
  - PROMOTION - BROUCHURE 1946., Folder 5 (Box Box 64)
  - GUIDE TO REGIONAL THEATER MAP., Folder 6 (Box Box 64)